zipker.com 2018-03-04

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Zipker.com value the worth of customers’ trust that they have in us while shopping on zipker.com. This is something that insists us keeping the highest standards in order to secure transactions as well as information privacy of customers. Zipker.com is undoubtedly a credible website that is owned and controlled by Zipker Online Services Private Limited. We have designed a Privacy Policy in that Zipker Online Services Private Limited is referred to as "we," "us," or "our" while users are referred to as "you", "your" or "user".

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Zipker.com has full right to change this Privacy Policy anytime just by posting the revised one in the "Privacy Policy" section of this site. The revised Privacy Policy will be applicable with immediate effect soon after being posted on the website. You are suggested to go through the website periodically that will let you have updated information about the Privacy Policy. Your regular use of our website will definitely be considered as your reference as well as acceptance of the revised terms of our Privacy Policy.

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

When you register with us at zipker.com and go through reviews as well as other features, we collect your personal information. Our executives gather your info such as name, email address and contact number while you register or place an order on our site. When you look for something on zipker.com, keywords will automatically be gathered at some secured location in order to improve our search results. Other than this, when you go through zipker.com, our systems collect info all about the personal info about your computer such as IP address. Kindly keep in mind that your IP address does not identify you personally.

All of the products and services that have been made available on zipker.com are not designed for children in any manner. Neither we collect any personal details from children nor sell anything to children.

**Usage of Information and Sharing**

Our Legal Necessities -Zipker.com reserve sole right to reveal your personal info if required: (1) Abide by the legal rules and regulations or legal process processed on Zipker Online Services Private Limited; (2) defend the property or rights of zipker.com; (3) in order to ensure abidance to our Terms & Conditions. Zipker Online Services Private Limited collaborates with law enforcement as well as other third parties to implement laws, intellectual property and other rights. Moreover, Zipker Online Services Private Limited reserve the rights to take legal action by reporting any suspicious or illegal activity to the law enforcement for prosecution.

Communication: Our executives are free to send you information of upcoming or latest services, products and updates. In case, you don’t want to receive any such information, you can very well opt to deny for receiving it just by sending a mail at [customercare@zipker.com.](mailto:customercare@zipker.com)

Payments: If you are a credit or debit card holder, your name and card number along with billing details will be sent to the concerned and applicable financial institution.

No unauthorized person or any organization is allowed to use any kind of information which is collected from you through zipker.com.

If you think that any of your information that we are collecting from you is wrong or incomplete, feel free to send us an email at the earliest. Our executives will quickly correct the mentioned incorrect information.

Zipker.com may also contain few links that may direct you to other websites. Kindly note that soon after leaving our website, Privacy Policy of zipker.com will no longer be applicable and it will be subjected to the Privacy Policy of the website that you will be using later.

**Third Parties**

We never disclose any kind of personal information of our customers to the third parties. Zipker.com reserve right to use any information for its own purposes, aggregate info which does not identify you personally in any manner. Moreover, we don’t share your collected information with the business partners, advertisers, sponsors, etc.

**Business Transfers**

We have right to disclose any personal information about the users of zipker.com as part of any merger, debt financing, acquisition, sale of company assets and in any event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information could be transferred to any third party as one of our business assets.

**Multifaceted Privacy Issues**

Children that are less than eighteen years old are not allowed to use our website and if found to use, it will be considered a legal offence. We ensure you not to collect any kind of information from children under the age of eighteen years. Other than this, no part of zipker.com has been designed to draw the attention of underage customers. Though we sell children's products also, but that are to be purchased by adults only. Children under eighteen years are allowed to use our website under observation or guidance of parents or guardian.

**Cookies**

Cookies are known as small pieces of information that are saved by your own browser on your system. These are used in order to record several aspects of your visit as well as helping zipker.com for providing you uninterrupted service. We don’t use cookies to save your personal information for any outside use.

Web server of Zipker automatically recognizes the following for every user: Browser type and Operating system information, Host origin of the request, Page viewed, Session data, Referrer, etc.

Zipker Online Services Private Limited use cookies to assure zipker.com runs on your computer and you are free to access content available on our website. Cookies never store your credit card information or passwords.

**Advertising**

**Zipker.com has full rights to send promotional SMS to registered users. All users who have registered on Zipker.com might receive promotional SMS at any time.**

For advertising online, we use remarketing with Google. Third party vendors including Google, show you ads available on the internet. Zipker as well as third-party vendors, including Google use first-party cookies (Google Analytics cookie) as well as third-party cookies (Double Click cookie) together to provide information, optimizing, and serving ads that are based on somebody's previous visits to zipker.com.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

We provide you opportunity to choose receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from zipker.com on behalf of our business partners and from Zipker Online Services Private Limited in general after setting up an account.

For any kind of queries regarding this Privacy Policy, just get in touch with us at[customercare@zipker.com.](mailto:customercare@zipker.com)
